GUILHERME MORONE ARAUJO

Software Engineer

- @ guimorone@gmail.com
- ∂ https://guimorone.github.io

- https://www.linkedin.com/in/guimorone
- Recife, Pernambuco, Brazil



EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer

Neurotech

04/2024 - Present

Full-time

- In general, using skills in backend development (FastAPI), data engineering, Terraform, Git, Airflow and cloud computing (AWS).
- · Collaborate with cross-functional teams to achieve project goals.
- · Ensure high-quality, scalable application development.
- Using Amazon Web Services such as Lambda, DynamoDB, EC2, Athena, S3 and more.

Software Engineer

Jalan

= 04/2024 - 05/2024

Full-time

 Worked as a Full Stack developer using VueJS and Quasar along with Python and Lambda Functions (AWS).

Mobile Engineer

aca.sc

= 03/2024 - 03/2024

Freelancer

 Worked as a Mobile Engineer in a Freelancer project (aca.so mobile app) using React Native.

Software Enginner

Oncase

m 02/2022 - 12/2023

 ${\mathscr O}$ https://www.oncase.com.br

Started as an intern and then worked full-time

- Developed Big Data applications with a focus on high efficiency, scalability, and low cost.
- Developed frontend applications using React (JavaScript, TypeScript and HTML/CSS) and Redux.
- Implemented backend functionality using Python frameworks Flask and Django.
- Implemented effective CI/CD pipelines for seamless integration and deployment through Docker and GitHub Actions.
- In general, utilized skills in web development (Django, React and HTML/CSS), data engineering, CI/CD, Docker, GitHub Actions, and cloud computing.
- Collaborated with cross-functional teams to achieve project goals.
- Enhanced customer relationships through the delivery of top-notch solutions.
- Ensured high-quality and scalable application development.
- Hosted applications on Google Cloud Platform using Cloud Run and Artifact Registry.
- Utilized Amazon Web Services for hosting, leveraging services like Amplify, Route53, and Lambda.

SUMMARY

Originally from Rio but now based in Recife, I've had the privilege of growing up in two vibrant cities

My passions are as diverse as my background, ranging from an avid love for games and books to an insatiable curiosity for travel and technology.

Furthermore, I am always eager to explore new opportunities and challenges that can help me grow both as a professional and as a person, fueled by my passion for learning and applying new technologies to solve real-world problems. I have been working on Software Development since 2022. Not only that, but I am used to developing Big Data applications that demand high efficiency, scalability, and low cost. All my projects demanded skills in web development, data engineering, CI/CD, Docker, GitHub Actions, and cloud computing, in order to deliver quality solutions to clients.

SKILLS

Pytho	n C/C++	Java	Haskell
Go	Ruby Ja	vaScript/Ty _l	peScript
Web D	evelopment	Django	React
Flask	FastAPI	Node	CI/CD
Git	GitHub Act	ions Doc	ker
Terraf	orm Airfl	ow AWS	GCP
React	Native F	utter HT	ML/CSS
JQuer	y Linux	Database	s SQL
Postgi	reSQL Me	ongoDB	

LANGUAGES

LANGUAGES		
Portuguese Native		•••
English Proficient		
German Beginner		

EXPERIENCE

Mobile Engineer

InSpace

= 08/2022 - 10/2022

Freelancer

 Identification of objects (censored specificity) from a mobile camera for legal purposes.

Game Developer

Educandus Tecnologia Educacional

= 06/2021 - 10/2021

Internship

 I have worked on web apps (educational simulators) using Construct 3 software and JavaScript mainly.

Game Developer

Educandus Tecnologia Educacional

= 05/2020 - 12/2020

Internship

 I have worked as a game developer using Construct 3 software and JavaScript, building educational games for students from preschool to high school levels.

EDUCATION

Bachelor, Computer Engineering

Federal University of Pernambuco GPA (CR) 9.07 / 10.0

Recife, Pernambuco, Brazil

· Expect to graduate by August 2024.